

Lot 4 Rovodrau, Pacific Harbor. Serua, Fiji

□ (+679) 7455618 | ☑ timothyfiji@gmail.com | 🌴 timothyfiji.github.io | 🖸 timothyfiji | 🛅 ahkoy

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

# Summary.

Self taught web developer specializing in front-end/infrastructure with 3+ years in web design and development. Super nerd who loves the WWW, WordPress and all things Open-Source. Interested in developing time-saving and problem-solving tools for issues currently faced by the people of Fiji.

# Work Experience

F1 Mobile Solutions Suva, Fiji

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

• Front end web developer using HTML5, CSS3 and JS to develope responsive online websites and applications

Matata Pacific Suva, Fiji

SENIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER Dec 2015 - Dec. 2018

- · Creation of websites and applications using HTML5, CSS3, JS and the Wordpress CMS
- Maintenance and management of all sites
- Content layout and design
- Conduct security and site performance audits
- Ensure secure backups for all sites

FijiFirst Suva, Fiji

Online Engineering Oct 1 - Nov 14

- Live video streaming and photography
- · Media archiving
- · Website management and maintenance

### **Living Waters Mission School**

Navua, Fiji

Jan 2013 - Sep. 2015

Consultant August 2018 - PRESENT

- Website Development
- Integration and management of booking management system

# Education

# FNU (Fiji National University) - TAFE NSW Partner Program

Suva, Fiji

DIPLOMA OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY NETWORKING ICA50411

Aug. 2010 - Feb. 2012

• Graduated with distinction under the FNU/TAFE partner program.

# Ski**lls**

**Web Development** Wordpress, HTML5, CSS3, JS, Bootstrap

eCommerce WooCommerce. PayPal
Devloper Tools GitHub, Source Tress, Brackets
Analytics/Reporting Google Analytics, Data Studio, HotJar

**Operating Systems** Windows, OSX, Ubuntu, Fedora, Pop OS, Linux Server, Win Server 2012

**Design/Photography** Photoshop, Sketch, Shotcut **Communication Tools** Slack, Google Suite, Microsoft Office



### FijiFirst - fijifirst.com

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

- · Responsible for the development of the FijiFirst official website
- Coordinate with public relations team for the creation of content and post articles
- Maintenance and site updates

### Fiji National Development Plan - fijindp.gov.fj

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

- Responsible for the development of the Fiji National Development Plan official website
- · Maintenance and site updates

## Fiji Museum - fijimuseum.org

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

- Responsible for the development of the Fiji Museum official website
- Coordinate with public relations team for the creation of content
- Maintenance and site updates

### Fiji National Sports Commission - fijisports.com

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

- · Responsible for the development of the Fiji Sports Commission official website
- Coordinate with public relations team for the creation of content and post articles
- Maintenance and site updates

### Maritime Safety Authority Of Fiji - msaf.com

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

- Responsible for the development of the Maritime Safety Authority Of Fiji official website
- Coordinate with public relations team for the creation of content and post articles
- Maintenance and site updates

#### **Bulalicious Activewear - bulalicious.com**

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

- · Responsible for the development of the Bulalicious Activewear eCommerce official website
- Design and layout of content
- Maintenance and site updates

#### Petero Civoniceva Foundation - peterosfoundation.com

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

- Responsible for the development of the Petero Civoniceva Foundation official website
- Design and layout of content
- · Maintenance and site updates

#### **CArche Studio - carchstudio.com**

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

- Responsible for the development of the CArch Studio official website
- Design and layout of content
- · Maintenance and site updates

### Viti Voyaging - voyaging.org.fj

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

- Responsible for the development of the Viti Voyaging official website
- Design and layout of content
- Maintenance and site updates

## Rotary Pacific Water for Life Foundation - rotarypacificwater.org

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER

- Responsible for the development of the Rotary Pacific Water for Life Foundation official website
- Coordinate with public relations team for the creation of content and post articles
- Design and layout of content
- Maintenance and site updates